[{"answer": "Right.", "docId": "130625pmt", "aSentId": 32, "question": "How significant could that be, of Trayvon Martin's DNA I should say?", "qSentId": 31}, {"answer": "I was going to try to seal the chest wound, sir.", "docId": "130625pmt", "aSentId": 45, "question": "And what would be the purpose of Saran wrap and Vaseline?", "qSentId": 44}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, because the law so much favors the defense, I mean, this is one of the best self-defense statutes for a defendant I've ever seen and it's one of the most pro-defense states in America when it comes to raising self- defense.", "docId": "130625pmt", "aSentId": 75, "question": "Tom Mesereau, from all that you've seen so far, would you rather be in the defense or the prosecution camp?", "qSentId": 74}, {"answer": "Well, yes, and also remember, the burden of proof which applies in every state of America is beyond any reasonable doubt.", "docId": "130625pmt", "aSentId": 92, "question": "But this is where, Thomas, that Florida is probably the best possible place in America that George Zimmerman could wish to be tried because, as you say, the statute of law there is so heavily skewed in his favor?", "qSentId": 91}, {"answer": "Well, I think their heart must go out to the parents, especially the mother of the deceased Trayvon Martin.", "docId": "130625pmt", "aSentId": 105, "question": "How much could that in the end sway, do you think, this final decision?", "qSentId": 104}, {"answer": "Well, I think you're absolutely right, Piers, me included.", "docId": "130625pmt", "aSentId": 142, "question": "Do you think it's right that she'd been thrown to the wolves in the way that she has?", "qSentId": 141}, {"answer": "Well, as I said, I think we've mentioned -- we made tremendous progress, but I think we also see how the president has been treated when people stand up in Congress and say you lie.", "docId": "130625pmt", "aSentId": 152, "question": "I've asked this to a few guests before, but do you believe in the context of all this going on this week, is America in your view a more or less racist country since Barack Obama first got elected president?", "qSentId": 151}, {"answer": "Hey, doing great, Piers.", "docId": "130625pmt", "aSentId": 178, "question": "Joel, how are you how?", "qSentId": 177}, {"answer": "You know, I was like millions of other Americans.", "docId": "130625pmt", "aSentId": 183, "question": "What were you thinking standing there watching this guy risking his life?", "qSentId": 182}, {"answer": "You know, I didn't really think about it.", "docId": "130625pmt", "aSentId": 195, "question": "If he had fallen, what would you have said?", "qSentId": 194}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, I prayed that God would give him strength and skill and that the gifts God had given him would come out to the full, that he would have focus and not be distracted -- just he would be at his best and the top of his game.", "docId": "130625pmt", "aSentId": 210, "question": "What did you say to him?", "qSentId": 209}, {"answer": "It really is.", "docId": "130625pmt", "aSentId": 239, "question": "Pretty awesome, isn't it?", "qSentId": 238}, {"answer": "I didn't know that, but maybe I will!", "docId": "130625pmt", "aSentId": 248, "question": "Are you going to be buying a pair of his jeans, which have now become the hottest jeans apparently in America?", "qSentId": 247}, {"answer": "Oh, I would love to.", "docId": "130625pmt", "aSentId": 261, "question": "Will you be with him every step of the way on these?", "qSentId": 260}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130625pmt", "aSentId": 289, "question": "What is going on in his head right now?", "qSentId": 288}, {"answer": "I -- the one thing I can tell you is it's not an addiction to something like a high -- high risk that sort of thing.", "docId": "130625pmt", "aSentId": 292, "question": "What's going on in this guy's head?", "qSentId": 291}, {"answer": "And many --", "docId": "130625pmt", "aSentId": 301, "question": "So it's fame?", "qSentId": 300}, {"answer": "They learn to perhaps be more circumspect and careful but they don't change substantively.", "docId": "130625pmt", "aSentId": 322, "question": "And we can have one of the most powerful political positions in America, held by somebody who will be sending -- let's be honest -- photos of his wiener to other strange women?", "qSentId": 321}, {"answer": "Does not work.", "docId": "130625pmt", "aSentId": 401, "question": "Does that work?", "qSentId": 400}, {"answer": "I'm not getting 460 calories.", "docId": "130625pmt", "aSentId": 422, "question": "From America?", "qSentId": 421}, {"answer": "Listen, your point is well taken.", "docId": "130625pmt", "aSentId": 450, "question": "It's all very well, you're saying no to the yummy but I mean, you take the yummy out of life, what are you left with?", "qSentId": 449}, {"answer": "Well, because I found out the facts and the facts are my initial thinking was like most Americans.", "docId": "130625pmt", "aSentId": 499, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 498}, {"answer": "But that's a bizarre argument.", "docId": "130625pmt", "aSentId": 517, "question": "Sanjay Gupta, who's seen as a very respected medical guy, he's very firmly, look, there is no evidence that he's seen that marijuana is any more harmful than alcohol or tobacco, and on that basis, why should it be treated differently?", "qSentId": 516}, {"answer": "Well, that's the issue.", "docId": "130625pmt", "aSentId": 543, "question": "Are those -- are those limbs, are those organizations going to pick up cannabis?", "qSentId": 542}, {"answer": "I didn't say that.", "docId": "130625pmt", "aSentId": 549, "question": "What am I left with?", "qSentId": 548}, {"answer": "Piers, obviously it did not work and it's not working now.", "docId": "130625pmt", "aSentId": 584, "question": "Did it work and are you in favor of legalizing cannabis?", "qSentId": 583}, {"answer": "Well, let's ask Patrick Kennedy to answer that very question.", "docId": "130625pmt", "aSentId": 600, "question": "You know, I'd be curious to find out how -- Mr. Kennedy, how prison helped you beat addiction?", "qSentId": 599}, {"answer": "The good news is those aren't our two only options.", "docId": "130625pmt", "aSentId": 627, "question": "Which is -- which is less harmful to America's national interest?", "qSentId": 626}]